Here we go... Upokami!
This time we have with us Ruri Hiromoto of Ocha-no-Ma
and Ruri Hiromoto of Ocha-no-Ma and Sumi Tashiro of Ocha-no-Ma.
This show is about the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Our recording, rehearsals, and more.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
So let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I'm Hiromoto.
I've been cooking more and more since I first appeared on Hello Kitchen.
I've been cooking more often.
It's wonderful! Thank you!
I didn't do much cooking before.
Hello Kitchen has made me cook more and more.
I've been cooking a lot more recently, like baked codfish with foil.
I've been making and wrapping dumplings.
But when I made the dumplings
I was satisfied just by making them.
I didn't cook them and they're sitting in the fridge.
I want some! I'll bake them.
Sue will cook them for you.
Thank you.
Do you want to eat with us?
Yes, I will.
But I think it's really great that you're actually using what you've learned.
Yes, we are.
Hello Project's winter tour is over.
I've had a lot of opportunities to reflect on myself.
I've been watching videos and looking back.
And also voice training.
I had a voice training with a teacher.
I have a teacher who tells me what I can do to improve my voice.
I'm trying my best to improve my voice through trial and error.
I've realized how important voice training is during this period.
You learned a lot at the Hello Project concert, and you've been thinking about what you can do to make the most of it.
I think it really stuck, didn't it? It really stuck. So I thought it's important to change if I'm going to do voice training.
Let's step up day by day. I'll do my best.
Let's start with the making of the music video for Manaka Inaba's overwhelming love music video, which will be released on April 17.
Please take a look at the making of the music video for Manaka Inaba's solo debut single, "Overwhelming Love," which will be released on April 17.
This video is pretty much a constant changeover.
It's really nice when she's dancing.
Sweets Punker
Sweets Punker.
The music video shooting for Overwhelming Love has begun. So we are dancing fully from the beginning.
It was quite difficult to get into the mood of the dance in the morning, and I personally felt that my eyes weren't open because I hadn't taken my caffeine,
But the teachers and various staff members told me that I was perfectly cute, so I am confident that I will do my best from this morning with a truly overwhelming sense of love and worldview.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Steak Make Steak Make Steak Make But I can't interrupt
Up School Steak Makeup Cue up Steak Makeup Cue up Steak Makeup
Emotional Recovery Burn in between Let's Burn Baby
Up School Steakmaking Can't wait to get started
What will it be like?
Up school Steak Makeup Don't get too worked up
Ah, always clean Cleaner
Let's go to life
This is upschool Steak Makeup Cuba Up Steak Makeup
This is definitely Steak Makeup No one can get in the way
Up School Steak Makeup Cue Bar Up Steak Makeup
Emotional recovery, in-between, let's burn, Baby
Up School Steak Makeup It can't be helped that it's starting
Shock What will it be like
Up school Steak Makeup Don't worry about it
Ah, always so clean Cleaner
It's just you, it's just you, it's just you, it's just you, it's just you, it's just you, it's just you, it's just you, it's just you, it's just you, it's just you
It's all about me
Yes, itadakimono-itadakimono-it was marshmallows
Cut!
I tried a little too hard.
Thank you for watching!
So all the shooting for the overwhelming love music video is over!
It was a lot of fun!
Anyway, as the title says, this song is about overwhelming love.
This song is about overwhelming love, absolute love.
It's a song about overwhelming love, absolute love.
My name is Mana, which means "love" in Japanese, and I use the kanji for "love" in my name.
I use the kanji character for love in my name and it means "love is fragrant" and I read it as "Managawa".
So when I received this song, I was very happy to hear the word "love" in it.
I thought about how to express this love in my own way.
I don't know who the other girl is, the guy or the girl, but I think it's about the person you love, no matter how much you resist it.
I don't know who the guy or girl is, but to the person she loves, no matter how hard she tries to resist, she can't do it, because she already loves him or her.
I don't know who the guy or girl is, but I think she's in love with the person she loves.
It's a song about the love that you can't help but love, no matter how much you resist.
So I made a lot of faces to the camera to convey that.
I tried to make a lot of expressions saying "I love you" to the camera.
I hope that people watching the song can understand that.
We had a lot of discussions together, not only about the lyrics but also about the music.
We discussed not only the lyrics, but also the music together, and I was able to make requests such as, "I personally prefer a more sparkling sound here.
I'd like to hear a little more sparkle here and there.
The chorus was supposed to have an exotic sound, but I think it would have been better to have a sparkling sound rather than that.
I thought it was easy for me to get emotionally involved in the song.
I thought it would be easier for me to get emotionally involved in the song.
The arrangement was done just the way I wanted it.
Anyway, I love this song, so I hope you enjoy it as much as I do.
I hope you enjoy the world of this song as much as I do.
Please check out the details of the song and watch it a lot!
Yes, I've seen the video.
I can really feel Inaba-san's love for the song.
In filming the music video, he used a lot of backgrounds and various kinds of images to create a lot of dance scenes.
I think he did a lot of dance scenes in many different kinds of videos.
I think they did a lot of dance scenes in many different kinds of images, but in every single image, I could see 100% of Manaka Inaba's dance and love.
You can see her love.
I really enjoyed it.
I think it was a really wonderful making-of video.
How was it for you, Sumiya?
Well, I really enjoyed it, too.
I think we took a lot of pictures.
But even so, I was really impressed with the way you managed your facial expressions and the sharpness of your dancing.
I was really impressed with the way she managed her facial expressions and the sharpness of her dancing.
And she was really cute.
You were really cute.
Even when we weren't shooting music videos
Inaba's cuteness overflowed even when she wasn't filming the music video, and it was really great.
This is the making of Manaka Inaba's overwhelming love music video shooting.
This is overwhelming love, sudden overwhelming love
Absolutely wonderful and no one can get in the way!
Overwhelming love, sudden overwhelming love
Emotions are now at capacity and
I'm always on your side
Next, here we go!
Ami Tanimoto, Marin Fukuda, Dance Lecture
In this corner, they will give you a lecture on the choreography of the choruses of songs other than the singles!
Let's take a look!
I'm Ami Tanimoto and Marin Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory, and I'm going to give you a lecture on the choreography of the choruses of Tsubaki Factory's non-single songs.
So this time, let's take a look at the choreography for the second step.
I'd like to teach you the choreography for "Ai ha ai desu kudasiteru" from "Second Step.
Well, this song is very cute and has a lot of catchy choreography.
And it's really easy to learn, so I'm sure you'll be able to remember it soon.
I hope you will give it a try!
So, first of all, we'd like to dance to the song.
♪ ♪
♪~
My stain will escape
Kindness doesn't diminish.
No bargaining, no confidence, it's a sign
Love needs love now
Ah Ah Ah Ah
I'd like to give you a lecture.
First of all, before the chorus.
There's a sound like "clang clang clang".
And the hands are like penguins.
Like a penguin
Like a penguin.
If you step on the right foot first, you'll end up with a good feeling.
From there
Yes, sir.
If you're serious
Yay! But first, put your hands in a piece.
Close, close, close, sideways, sideways.
Pan, pan, pan, pan, like that.
And the feet go "pan, pan, pan.
Yay! Center of gravity is on this side.
Open, close, right over there, center of gravity.
If you're serious...
Then you do it twice, like this, twice, and next, you wipe your hands like this.
Like a wipe. Like a wiper.
Like windshield wipers on a car. Like that, right and left.
After you do right, left, and left, next is the box step.
Then you do the box step.
Show your love, and when you step, move your hands at the same time.
A little difficult. - A little difficult.
If you're big, it's easy. Show your partner.
Wonton. We'll do this twice more.
Then, after that, we'll move up from the bottom and down from the top.
I'm going to do it while stamping my feet.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
Do do do do do. Repeat one more time.
Repeat again. That's my step.
I'm not confident in my beats, and I'm not confident in my tactics, and I'm not confident in my moves.
I'm not confident in my beats, and I'm not confident in my tactics, and I'm not confident in my confidence, and I'm not confident in my beat.
So before that, there's a little bit of walking choreography.
So I'd like to start from the beginning.
I might forgive you in a second if you praise me.
If you're serious, it's easy.
But you have to show some love, even if it's just in your attitude.
Manipulate him. Stop him.
You're going to get away with it.
You can't be nice to someone and expect them to be nice to you.
It's all about tactics and confidence.
Tomorrow, love needs love now.
That leads us to...
Yes, ma'am.
And here.
The part "Love is seeking love now" is also very simple.
I think you've mastered it, haven't you? I think the choreography is pretty simple.
So let's dance with us.
My stain will escape.
Gentleness is not a hermon
I'm not interested in games.
It's a proof
Love needs love now
How was it?
Did I do it?
I think you did it.
I think so.
The point of this song is the piece.
There are a lot of pieces in the chorus.
And also in the part of "Love is now", there are a lot of pieces.
So, please make a lot of peace and dance happily.
Even if it's just your hands at a concert or something.
It's a very cute choreography, so I'd like you to do it!
I'd love to see you do it!
That's all for now, this is Ami Tanimoto and
and Maman Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory.
Bye bye!
Yes, it's a very catchy choreography
The choreography is so cute that you can imitate it
It made us want to dance with them!
Yes, you taught us slowly and carefully by watching the video together.
It was so easy to understand!
It's so easy to understand and it's already in your head.
When this song is played at the concert, please dance along with us.
Please try to dance along with them!
That's all for this Ami Tanimoto Marin Fukuda's dance lecture!
Take care of yourself and don't overdo it!
Ruri Hiromoto of Ocha-no-Oma and
and Sumire Tashiro of Ocha-no-Oma
Next, here we go!
Tsubaki Factory: Epilogue to the Rainy Day Instrumental Recording
From Tsubaki Factory's latest album
Please check out the guitar recording of "Epilogue to the Rainy Day" from Tsubaki Factory's newest album!
Are you ready to coach, Mr. Asahi?
Okay, I'll take a guess inside.
I'm going to try to find the point while I'm moving 5 cm 10 cm.
"The window opens, in place of my unspoken selfishness
Tears of love, fierce, hold back the stars.
I see love, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
(What a cold sky, even if it's one person at a time)
(I really want to touch you, I'm not enough)
(Looks like I'm full of it)
Thank you for watching.
I think you played the intro with the "ts" in the pattern, "chan ts chan".
At first, it sounded like "jan-jan-jan-jan-jan-jan".
I see... I prefer it if you keep on stretching it out.
Yes, yes, yes.
is ideal.
So, there's the F-sharp before the 2nd chorus, and the F-sharp in the qui...
Before the 2nd chorus...
It's bar 88.
Yes, yes, yes, like this
I thought it would be really cool if you could make the crescendo of
Let's see... "Jan-jan-jan-jan"...
That's the part where you decide.
That's right.
Jan-jan-jan-jan-jan-jan-jan.
From here, crescendo for 3 bars.
Over the course of three bars.
A little over two bars.
Around here, okay.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
~~
I'm sorry, I need to ask you one question.
Um, I'm on measure 80, G major center.
I'd like to have the top note be a G.
It was an F sharp there.
~~
Yes, that's the F sharp.
Yes, sir.
~~
He says it's looking good.
Okay, here we go.
~~
Okay, let's, uh, take it from the top, just one...
~~~
Morning, the turbulence is so fierce, it's holding you back.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I'll wake up and I'll cry I'll be so surprised I won't be able to relax
I've touched you more than you've touched me.
Let me see your sadne
I'm just a little concerned about the minor right here.
Yes, I got it. I'll listen here.
Inter five.
Five.
Okay, here you go.
As I said, we're going to play one more from A9.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
I can't see it from now until the end
Now the disorder is...
It's the tone that makes it sound so real.
I know, right? And the single chord is the same as the chorus.
Then the chorus? I'll pick up the video.
I'm going to pick up a little footage.
I love you.
I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you
I'll cry with each of you
Even if it's one at a time
If you love me more, be quiet
~ I think it went so well
I think that went well.
Then this guitar does its job
And...
Intro.
~~
Thank you for watching
I think it's good
Maybe I should do sound effects at the end.
Sound effects, yeah.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to include inter-two feedback.
I don't know if it's a good idea or not.
Mr. Asahi, you'll get your money's worth.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I brought my arm guitar.
This is it...
It's going up from zero.
Imagine that for a moment.
I understand it very well.
Thank you very much for watching.
I think this is good.
You're good at this, aren't you?
Okay, we're done.
Thank you very much.
My name is KOUGA, arranger.
I'm a guitarist asaiyaso.
For Tsubaki Factory.
on the song "Snow Planetarium" by Tsubaki Factory.
I've played guitar on a song called "Snow Planetarium" by Tsubaki Factory.
This song is also one of my favorites.
It's minor, up-tempo, and a little bit sad.
It's a minor, up-tempo song with a bit of sadness.
It's a song with a bit of sadness in it.
I tried to make it sad and melancholy, but I also tried to make it pop and rock.
but with a bit of pop and rock.
I think I was able to blend it well.
And finally, I did what I do best.
I used a lot of different phrases.
Can I put this in here? Can I put it in? Like, "Can I put it in here?
I made him put in more and more phrases.
I'm sorry.
No, it was great.
That's what I was looking for.
I'm so happy that you did that.
I was so happy.
I thought I was overdoing it.
I thought I was overdoing it and I was holding it back.
I felt like you released all of them.
I'm very happy to hear you say that.
We met for the first time today.
We're talking well together, but...
Today's recording session went well.
Thank you very much.
So, I've seen the recording of musical instruments.
I used an acoustic guitar, an electric guitar, and another electric guitar.
The acoustic guitar has a very delicate and sad feeling.
The electric guitar has a really rock feeling.
I felt the rock part of the sad, rock-like feeling to the maximum.
And the subtlety of the arrangement you mentioned was really cool.
I understand.
The guitar technique is really amazing.
I was really impressed by your guitar skills.
Seeing everyone in the studio discussing ideas and stuff like that, it really sunk in and I realized that this kind of great work is made by everyone sharing their ideas and opinions like this.
That was the epilogue of Tsubaki Factory's guitar recording.
It's cool that you're working so hard!
It's time for Ruri Hiromoto and Sumire Tashiro to say goodbye to Apkami!
We've seen a lot of footage this time.
I, Tashiro, was impressed by the making of Manaka Inaba's "Overwhelming Love" music video.
I was able to learn all about how Inaba-san really manages his facial expressions, and how he is so cute and carefree in his dancing.
I learned a lot from watching the making of the music video.
Next time I shoot a music video, I want to do my best with Inaba-san in mind.
Yes, and I, Hiromoto, really like instrumental recording.
When I come here to record, and when I watch it at home.
I am always very moved by the instrumental recordings.
I'm not the type of person who can handle an instrument well when I'm making it.
I'm not the type of person who can handle an instrument well
I'm not the type of person who can handle an instrument well, so I'm really impressed by the professional player's fingertips and sense of sound.
I think it's really cool to see a professional player's fingertips and sense of sound, and the way they listen to you.
I wonder if I can become like them.
I hope I can be influenced by them and train my own sense of sound.
At Atami, you can get a behind-the-scenes look at the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We'll take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel so we can show you what you don't normally see!
This time, our partners in Appukami are Ruri Hiromoto of Ocha-no-Oma and Sumire Tashiro of Ocha-no-Oma!
Good bye.
Next time on Apu-Kami, we'll be going behind the scenes of Hello Project Hina Fest 2024!
and the recording of Tsubaki Factory's latest album "Third Moment"!
Please look forward to it!
Next time: Hello Project's album Third Moment!